

Arvin Dela Cruz

Technical Support

Phone: (514) 754-3125 Email: chizarvin@gmail.com LinkedIn: arvindelacruz30

OBJECTIVE

I am a Computing Support and Networks graduating student and I would be interested in Internship opportunity with Hitachi ID Systems. I am detailoriented, organized a strong team player, flexible and able to multi task and I am also good with people. I believe that my experience in providing support technically and interpersonally would make me an ideal fit.

SKILLS

Operating Systems: Linux/Unix & Windows

Web-based Application: HTML 5, CSS3 and Bootstrap

Programming Tools: Python

Office Tools: Access, Power-point Microsoft Word & Excel

OTHER SKILLS

- Works effectively in a team environment
- Strong problem solving and organizational skills and able to multitask
- ➤ Languages: English and Tagalog/Basic French

EDUCATION

COMPUTING SUPPORT AND NETWORKS

SEP 2017 - FEB 2019 Verdun Adult and Career Centre, Canada Major: Typography GPA: 3.80/4.00

GRADUATE IN HIGH SCHOOL

2016-2017 James Lyng Adult Centre, Canada High School Diploma Attained

EXPERIENCE

GENERAL HELPER/BAKER | 2017-2018

Red Design Limited, San Diego, CA 91232

- > Followed recipes which make 100 pounds of cookie dough at a time.
- Operated baking machines and ovens.
- Mixed, prepared and baked bread and pastries.

MACHINE OPERATOR LEVEL 2 | 2013 - 2014

Matrix Media Limited, San Diego, CA 41262

- > Operated the packaging machine and boxing machine.
- Entered data for the NAV system.
- ➤ Troubleshooting

INVOLVEMENTS

> Online Web Development Boot camp: Web development course.

